<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrew Siah</title>
    <link>https://andrewsiah.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrew Siah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrewsiah.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pipenv Cheatsheet</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/pipenv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/pipenv/</guid>
      <description>Pipenv Cheat Sheet by Brad Traversy Install pipenv pip3 install pipenv Activate pipenv shell Check version of Python python --version Check path python &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; import sys &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; sys.executable quit() Install a package pipenv install camelcase Check local packages pipenv lock -r Uninstall a package pipenv uninstall camelcase Install a dev package pipenv install nose --dev Install from requirements.txt pipenv install -r ./requirements.txt Check security vulnerabilities pipenv check Check dependency graph pipenv graph Ignore pipfile pipenv install --ignore-pipfile Set lockfile - before deployment pipenv lock Exiting the virtualenv exit Run with pipenv pipenv run * </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badminton To Bring</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/badminton/</guid>
      <description> Shoes Racquet Shuttle Wallet Phone Towel Spare clothes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac Apps</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/apps/</guid>
      <description>Mac Apps  Ticktick Firefox Conda Kite Cisco anyconnect vpn Vscode Rectangle Backup and sync from google Zoom uTorrent web Spotify Whatsapp Soundcleod Selfcontrol imovie Discord vlc keepassxc Quickshade Notion  Brew  firebase git qt sass scrcpy hugo django  GeoDjango Dependencies  postgresql postgis gdal libgeoip spatialite-tools (if geodjango used with sqlite3)  Catalina Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sinus SOP</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/sinus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/sinus/</guid>
      <description> Eat (Spicy, Soup, Hot, Carbs) Drink (Water, Hot Tea) Pill (Zyrtec, Telfast) Shower (Hot) Sleep Rest Early and Long, to prevent damaging sinus and more days of being ill.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel To Pack</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/travel-to-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/travel-to-pack/</guid>
      <description> Currency Cash Misceallanous in To-Do List Clothes &amp;amp; Pants &amp;amp; Socks Underwear Cold weather wear Shoes/Slippers Skin Care Laundry Plastic Bag Towel Toiletries Laptop &amp;amp; Phone Charger Laptop &amp;amp; iPad Travel Adaptors Home Key &amp;amp; Cards Sim Card  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/questions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Me in 2 min I&amp;rsquo;m Andrew, a Malaysian Physics undergrad on a dual-degree programme between Columbia in NY and CityU in HK.
I&amp;rsquo;ve never been the smartest or the most talented in anything. I&amp;rsquo;m just curious and ask questions.
This is my favourite emoji 🤷‍♂️.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently on a gap year, till Sept 2021, documenting my autodidacy on Youtube and here.
I&amp;rsquo;ll love to make new friends, please reach out to me for anything!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/books/</guid>
      <description>Non-Fiction Read My notes are automatically generated from Play Books.
Highlights - Red: To apply in life. Yellow: Resonating notes. Green: Vocabulary to revise on.
 Deep Work - Cal Newport  A manifesto that argues how long duration of focused work will be a rare and valuable commodity. Especially in an upcoming world where it&amp;rsquo;s easier for everyone to be distracted (Social Media, Netflix, Youtube, etc).   Atomic Habits - James Clear  Argues that greatness comes from consistent grinding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/habits/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a productivity and habit geek, I can&amp;rsquo;t make do without a list of habits I&amp;rsquo;m pursuing now can I!
Instilling Currently  Wake up by 6am Deliberately practice Guitar for 5 min Cold Showers in the morning 5 min morning journals No phone before lunch Exercise daily Code daily Read daily (Anything) Write daily (Anything)  Someday Maybe  Stay off coffee for a month Greet someone new each day  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible List</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/impossible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/impossible/</guid>
      <description>Life  Own a motorcycle Get a pilot license  Fitness/Health Goals  Pull-Ups (Controlled)  5 10   Push-Ups (Controlled)  20 30   Join Spartan Challenge Run a Marathon  Half Full    Academic Goals  Independently finish Griffith&amp;rsquo;s  Electrodynamics Quantum Mechanics   Publish an academic paper Get 75% scholarship for Columbia (Currently funded USD 61,123 / 176,000) Graduate Summa Cum Laude Internship at DeepMind / OpenAI  Professional Goals  Get 1,000 blog visits Make my own website  Wordpress templated site (andrewsiah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/now/</guid>
      <description>Work Jobless 🤷‍♂️
Learning  Full Stack Web-Development Machine Learning Embedded Web App Bootstrap software startup  Leisure  Guitar Card-Throwing IMDB Top 100 Movie List Writing about movies and books Chess 1000 Elo  Self-Experimenting  Maker or Manager schedule My physical limits (in focus and exercise)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>I exist on the shoulders of giants. Shoulders of kind, loving, selfless saints who spent time with me, invested in me, guided me. To you all, I am eternally grateful. Thank you for making a difference in this little boy’s life. Thank you for making this world, a better place to live in.
The list and detail below is by no means complete – not even close. It is my small attempt in acknowledging the great people in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MEMSI 2021</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/memsi-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/memsi-2021/</guid>
      <description>Preface MEMSI is not a hackathon. MEMSI is not a business case competition. Heck, MEMSI does not even have monetary or opportunity prizes. No. The goal of MEMSI is to educate what entrepreneurship is like through simulation, immersing into one industry (for my year, it&amp;rsquo;s the aviation), and using the framework of Disciplined Entrepreneurship.
Teammates MEMSI filters their participants. There&amp;rsquo;s a simple interview and threshold one must pass (Year 3 and above).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMARTP goals</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/smartp-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/smartp-goals/</guid>
      <description>The importance of setting goals  Fail to plan, Plan to fail.
 I first heard the above quote when I was in high school, sometime around when I was 13. It sounded like a truism, then again, one that I intuitively related with. We don&amp;rsquo;t achieve goals we didn&amp;rsquo;t set out for. Running on the premises that:
 Life is filled with temptations and short-term candies Forgoing short-term temptations to put in effort takes conscious effort Any goals that are worth achieving requires effort and investment  Then, planning or setting goals is the battleplan to success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Moral Imperative to Show our Work</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/moral-imperative-to-show-our-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/moral-imperative-to-show-our-work/</guid>
      <description>Impostor Syndrome I struggle with impostor syndrome. Through this blog, youtube, and meeting others, I&amp;rsquo;ve always felt that it&amp;rsquo;s not in my place to contribute.
 &amp;ldquo;Who am I to speak here? There are better people out there who are more qualified, more helpful, and more charismatic than me.&amp;rdquo;
 The plot twist Recently, I stumbled upon an argument on why it&amp;rsquo;s our moral imperative to actually show our work. The premises are there</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits or Passion</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/habits-vs-passion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/habits-vs-passion/</guid>
      <description>Preface It&amp;rsquo;s been 2 months since I last published here and on youtube. What happened in that timeframe? I met great friends in ipoh, went to Jing Wei&amp;rsquo;s marriage, started developing my work site, and played chess (Loads of chess). Am I happy? Is that enough?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Marriage. What it simply is &amp; what it takes.</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/on-marriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/on-marriage/</guid>
      <description>The story As I stood on the side of the altar, observing my best friend stare down the aisle. Pianist starts playing Canon in D, and the bridesmaid leads the bride, gently and slowly, down the aisle. The bride and groom locks gaze, a pleasant smile hangs on their face. As the cousin of the bride and the bride reach the groom, the cousin hands the hand of the bride over to the groom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear Setting (A Model on Tim Ferriss&#39;s Framework)</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/fear-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/fear-setting/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Our decision making process is often irrational. Because we often only have a method of rationalizing the costs and benefits, but no method for rationalizing fear.
For an example, assume you want to explore asking an opposite gender out. The benefit, if successful, is being able to go out with the girl and know her better. The cost, if unsuccessful, is shame and time wasted from the rejection. Shame is temporal, exists larger in your imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Show Your Work</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/show-your-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/show-your-work/</guid>
      <description>Through my two years of studying at university, I have been graced with many opportunities. Friends who I scored Hackathons with; mentors who guided me on professional and private life matters; gracious recommendation letters that I received for my work; and interviews for jobs and scholarships that I’ve gotten from mutual friends.
What is the commonality above? That I have substance. Maybe not, I’m 100% sure there are many more out there who are more knowledgeable, with better GPA and a CV 10,000 lumen brighter than mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/markdown/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/archive/</guid>
      <description>archive</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
