<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrew Siah</title>
    <link>https://andrewsiah.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrew Siah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrewsiah.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How crowded is Columbia Dining right now</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/columbia-dining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/columbia-dining/</guid>
      <description>Find out here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipenv Cheatsheet</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/pipenv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/pipenv/</guid>
      <description>Pipenv Cheat Sheet by Brad Traversy Install pipenv pip3 install pipenv Activate pipenv shell Check version of Python python --version Check path python &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; import sys &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; sys.executable quit() Install a package pipenv install camelcase Check local packages pipenv lock -r Uninstall a package pipenv uninstall camelcase Install a dev package pipenv install nose --dev Install from requirements.txt pipenv install -r ./requirements.txt Check security vulnerabilities pipenv check Check dependency graph pipenv graph Ignore pipfile pipenv install --ignore-pipfile Set lockfile - before deployment pipenv lock Exiting the virtualenv exit Run with pipenv pipenv run * </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badminton To Bring</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/badminton/</guid>
      <description> Shoes Racquet Shuttle Wallet Phone Towel Spare clothes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac Apps</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/apps/</guid>
      <description>Mac Apps Ticktick Firefox Conda Kite Cisco anyconnect vpn Vscode Rectangle Backup and sync from google Zoom uTorrent web Spotify Whatsapp Soundcleod Selfcontrol imovie Discord vlc keepassxc Quickshade Notion Brew firebase git qt sass scrcpy hugo django GeoDjango Dependencies postgresql postgis gdal libgeoip spatialite-tools (if geodjango used with sqlite3) Catalina Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sinus SOP</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/sinus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/sinus/</guid>
      <description> Eat (Spicy, Soup, Hot, Carbs) Drink (Water, Hot Tea) Pill (Zyrtec, Telfast) Shower (Hot) Sleep Rest Early and Long, to prevent damaging sinus and more days of being ill. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel To Pack</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/travel-to-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/checklist/travel-to-pack/</guid>
      <description> Currency Cash Misceallanous in To-Do List Clothes &amp;amp; Pants &amp;amp; Socks Underwear Cold weather wear Shoes/Slippers Skin Care Laundry Plastic Bag Towel Toiletries Laptop &amp;amp; Phone Charger Laptop &amp;amp; iPad Travel Adaptors Home Key &amp;amp; Cards Sim Card </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/questions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Me in 2 min I&amp;rsquo;m Andrew, a Malaysian Physics undergrad on a dual-degree programme between Columbia in NY and CityU in HK.
I&amp;rsquo;ve never been the smartest or the most talented in anything. I&amp;rsquo;m just curious and ask questions.
This is my favourite emoji &amp;#x1f937;&amp;zwj;&amp;#x2642;&amp;#xfe0f;.
I love documenting my learnings on Youtube and here.
I did a gap year from 2020 - Sept 2021, while documenting my autodidacy on Youtube and here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/books/</guid>
      <description>Non-Fiction Read My notes are automatically generated from Play Books.
Highlights - Red: To apply in life. Yellow: Resonating notes. Green: Vocabulary to revise on.
Deep Work - Cal Newport A manifesto that argues how long duration of focused work will be a rare and valuable commodity. Especially in an upcoming world where it&amp;rsquo;s easier for everyone to be distracted (Social Media, Netflix, Youtube, etc). Atomic Habits - James Clear Argues that greatness comes from consistent grinding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/habits/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a productivity and habit geek, I can&amp;rsquo;t make do without a list of habits I&amp;rsquo;m pursuing now can I!
Instilling Currently Wake up by 6am Deliberately practice Guitar for 5 min Cold Showers in the morning 5 min morning journals No phone before lunch Exercise daily Code daily Read daily (Anything) Write daily (Anything) Someday Maybe Stay off coffee for a month Greet someone new each day </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible List</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/impossible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/impossible/</guid>
      <description>Life Own a motorcycle Get a pilot license Fitness/Health Goals Pull-Ups (Controlled) 5 10 Push-Ups (Controlled) 20 30 Join Spartan Challenge Run a Marathon Half Full Academic Goals Independently finish Griffith&amp;rsquo;s Electrodynamics Quantum Mechanics Publish an academic paper Get 75% scholarship for Columbia (Currently funded USD 61,123 / 176,000) Graduate Summa Cum Laude Internship at DeepMind / OpenAI Professional Goals Get 1,000 blog visits Make my own website Wordpress templated site (andrewsiah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/now/</guid>
      <description>Work Jobless &amp;#x1f937;&amp;zwj;&amp;#x2642;&amp;#xfe0f;
Learning Full Stack Web-Development Machine Learning Embedded Web App Bootstrap software startup Leisure Guitar Card-Throwing IMDB Top 100 Movie List Writing about movies and books Chess 1000 Elo Self-Experimenting Maker or Manager schedule My physical limits (in focus and exercise) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>I exist on the shoulders of giants. Shoulders of kind, loving, selfless saints who spent time with me, invested in me, guided me. To you all, I am eternally grateful. Thank you for making a difference in this little boy’s life. Thank you for making this world, a better place to live in.
The list and detail below is by no means complete – not even close. It is my small attempt in acknowledging the great people in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal of Financial Freedom is not Idleness</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/financial-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/financial-freedom/</guid>
      <description>FIRE Today, one of the key goals I hear from my peers is the goal to FIRE (Financially independent, retire early). There have been many proponents of it, and many detractors as well. Yet, one of the main reasons we hear why people want to retire is so they can wake up whenever they want, eat whatever they want, and travel wherever they want. See the world and chill.
Yet, we often hear from the other side that people who have reached FIRE find life to be dull, boring even, as if their life surmounts to nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to debug Pytorch/Deep Learning in VSCode</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/debugging-pytorch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/debugging-pytorch/</guid>
      <description>Debugging a PyTorch Script in Jupyter Notebook Here is a youtube guide video!
Open the Notebook: Open your .ipynb file directly in VSCode. Insert Breakpoints: In the margin next to the cell numbers, click to set breakpoints. Start the Jupyter Server: If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, start the Jupyter server by running a cell. Run the Cell in Debug Mode: Right-click on the cell with a breakpoint and select &amp;ldquo;Debug Cell&amp;rdquo; from the context menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to work when you don&#39;t want to</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/work-motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/work-motivation/</guid>
      <description>Working when unmotivated</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding P to SMART goals</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/smartp-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/smartp-goals/</guid>
      <description>The P that makes SMART goals, SMARTP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MEMSI 2021</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/memsi-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/memsi-2021/</guid>
      <description>A reflection on experience and lessons learnt through MEMSI 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Moral Imperative to Show our Work</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/show-our-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/show-our-work/</guid>
      <description>Why we Need to Document and Share our Work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits or Passion</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/habits-vs-passion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/habits-vs-passion/</guid>
      <description>Are we better off being habitual, or doing what our passion lead us to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Marriage. What it simply is &amp; what it takes.</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/on-marriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/on-marriage/</guid>
      <description>The simple take on marriage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear Setting (A Model on Tim Ferriss&#39;s Framework)</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/fear-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/fear-setting/</guid>
      <description>A framework for more rational decision making through understanding our fears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passion is a Woodfire</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/passion-woodfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/passion-woodfire/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the nature of passion as an ignitable and sustainable force</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I keep a List of my Failures.</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/failure-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/failure-cv/</guid>
      <description>Discover how a &amp;#39;Failure CV&amp;#39; can objectively foster growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining an affordable Blockchain-based Insurance</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/blockchain-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/blockchain-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Insurance Origin of Insurance You’re a sailor in 17th century Great Britain. Sailing the 7 seas for gold, gospel, and glory. Yet with all the treasures and adventure of sailing, it came with significant risks. With pirates lurking around for booties, lousy hygiene on board, terrible treatment to most sailors, unpredictable storms, and little to no healthcare on board, it’s not far-fetch to say a significant amount of sailors don’t return alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Show Your Work</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/show-your-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/blogs/show-your-work/</guid>
      <description>A post on why showing our work on the internet is the most powerful form of networking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/cheatsheet/markdown/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
