<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lists on Andrew Siah</title>
    <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lists on Andrew Siah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://andrewsiah.com/lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/books/</guid>
      <description>Non-Fiction Read My notes are automatically generated from Play Books.
Highlights - Red: To apply in life. Yellow: Resonating notes. Green: Vocabulary to revise on.
 Deep Work - Cal Newport Atomic Habits - James Clear Getting Things Done - David Allen Courage to be Disliked - Ichiro Kishimi The Checklist Manifesto - Atul Gawande  I have a compiled list of checklists here   Essentialism - Greg Mckeown Show Your Work - Austin Kleon How To Be Miserable - Randy J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/habits/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a productivity and habit geek, I can&amp;rsquo;t make do without a list of habits I&amp;rsquo;m pursuing now can I!
Instilling Currently  Wake up by 6am Deliberately practice Guitar for 5 min Cold Showers in the morning 5 min morning journals No phone before lunch Exercise daily Code daily Read daily (Anything) Write daily (Anything)  Someday Maybe  Stay off coffee for a month Greet someone new each day  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible List</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/impossible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/impossible/</guid>
      <description>Life  Own a motorcycle Get a pilot license  Fitness/Health Goals  Pull-Ups (Controlled)  5 10   Push-Ups (Controlled)  20 30   Join Spartan Challenge Run a Marathon  Half Full    Academic Goals  Independently finish Griffith&amp;rsquo;s  Electrodynamics Quantum Mechanics   Publish an academic paper Get 75% scholarship for Columbia (Currently funded USD 61,123 / 176,000) Graduate Summa Cum Laude Internship at DeepMind / OpenAI  Professional Goals  Get 1,000 blog visits Make my own website  Wordpress templated site (andrewsiah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/now/</guid>
      <description>Work Jobless 🤷‍♂️
Learning  Full Stack Web-Development Machine Learning Embedded Web App Bootstrap software startup  Leisure  Guitar Card-Throwing IMDB Top 100 Movie List Writing about movies and books Chess 1000 Elo  Self-Experimenting  Maker or Manager schedule My physical limits (in focus and exercise)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewsiah.com/lists/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>I exist on the shoulders of giants. Shoulders of kind, loving, selfless saints who spent time with me, invested in me, guided me. To you all, I am eternally grateful. Thank you for making a difference in this little boy’s life. Thank you for making this world, a better place to live in.
The list and detail below is by no means complete – not even close. It is my small attempt in acknowledging the great people in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
